Guide to the Sexuality in Society Ephemera, 1960-2015
Sexuality in Society Ephemera, 1960-2015
- Songs & Stories of Women booklet, a benefit for the Triangle Hospice, 2000; Durham, North Carolina (Box 15, Folder 37)
- The Works: Drugs, Sex & AIDS comic book, produced by the San Francisco AIDS Foundation, 1987; San Francisco, California (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Health for Gay Men pamphlet, published by the New York City Department of Health, 1972; New York, New York (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Safe Sex Explorer's "Action Packed" Starter Kit Handbook, draft for the GLAS Safe Sex Starter Kit, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Celebration '90: Gay Games III & Cultural Festival official program, 1990; Vancouver, Canada (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Captain Condom's Original Party Pack! Your Voyage into the Amazing World of Condoms! publication, 1991; San Francisco, California (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Ephemera from the San Francisco Lesbian/Gay Freedom Day Parade and Celebration., 1991; Includes numerous pamphlets and other informational materials regarding Asian-Americans and transvestites. San Francisco, California (Box 15, Folder 43)
- NGLTF's "Creating Change" 2003 Conference registration packet, 2003; Miami, Florida (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Erotic deck of cards (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Rainbow pin with buck, labeled "Bucks M.C. [motorcycle club] Present 2003 Santa Saturday", a charity raising event, November 29, 2003; New Hope, Pennsylvania (Box 15, Folder 46)
- Gay Liberation Supplement, Chicago, Illinois (Box 15, Folder 47)
- Clippings on Anita-Dances of Vice, a documentary about a dancer who scandalized Berlin in the 1920's., 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 48)
- "Homosexuality: 25 Questions & Answers" pamphlet, Los Angeles, California (Box 15, Folder 49)
- Safe sex packet handed out by ACT-UP Ithaca at the Summer 1990 Gay Picnic, Summer 1990; Ithaca, New York (Box 15, Folder 50)
- Lily Tomlin playbill, July 1981; Chicago (?) (Box 15, Folder 51)
- International Lesbian & Gay Association (IGLA) ephemera, 1989; Vienna, Austria (Box 15, Folder 52)
- Poster from the 1st Tokyo Lesbian and Gay Film Festival, and an "I Love You" condom, 1992; Tokyo, Japan (Box 15, Folder 53)
- "Macho Slut" pin, Pin from Pat Califia's book by the same name. (Box 15, Folder 54)
- Announcement of email list hosted at Cornell for gay/lesbian/bi South Asians, June 6, 1993; Ithaca, New York (Box 15, Folder 55)
- Course announcement flyer for "Lesbian and Gay Experience", taught by Mary Spooner and Dan Tsang, University of Michigan, 1977; Ann Arbor, Michigan (Box 15, Folder 56)
- Poster advertisement for "Intersexions: Queer Visual Culture at the Crossroads" conference, organized by CLAGS, November 2004; New York City (Box 15, Folder 57)
- Poster advertisement for "Transpolitics, social change, and justice" conference, organized by CLAGS, May 2005; New York City (Box 15, Folder 59)
- Label: "Warning: The Reader's Guide Excludes the Lesbian and Gay Press"; other handouts, 1992; From the American Library Association (ALA) Gay and Lesbian Task Force meeting (Box 15, Folder 58)
- Rainbow Connections: Dating Service, Undated; Ontario, Canada (Box 15, Folder 60)
- KARN Publications Garston, catalog, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 61)
- AIDS Topics for Judicial Training, NYC, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 62)
- Affirmation: Gay and Lesbian Mormons, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 63)
- Women's Center, Binghamton, New York, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 64)
- National Visibility Campaign for the Gay and Lesbian Vote mailing, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 65)
- Ithaca, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 66)
- Provincetown, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 67)
- Gay Academic Union, NUGS, New York City (from Mariposa Archives), 1973 (Box 15, Folder 68)
- Womanmade Products, Seneca Falls, New York, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 69)
- Nude male with grapes on "zebra" skin rug (stereo postcard with built-in viewer), Undated (Box 15, Folder 70)
- Edith Ann doll and DVD (Box 15)
- Gran Fury AIDS poster, designed for bus displays (Box 16)
- Memorabilia collected at San Francisco LGBT pride parade, June 28, 2015 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Memorabilia collected at Paris pride parade, 2015 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Anthony Weiner Doll Articles, 2011 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Anthony Weiner Doll, MU-1513 (Box 17)
- Small pride flag, MU-1510 (Box 17)
- Stuffed figure representing HIV, Undated; MU-2262 (Box 17)
- 2 t-shirts from March on Washington and The L Word shirt, donated by Nancy Law, 1993; MU-2259-2261 (Box 18)
- SF gay pride tank top - donated by an Ithaca woman, Ann Morse, 1993; MU-2272 (Box 18)
- Unique set of cardboard cutouts/magnets featuring Moe from Alison Bechdel’s cartoon strip Dykes to Watch out For and accessories - made by a lesbian couple, Ann Morse and Lynn Staack, ca. 1990's; MU-2271 (Box 19)
- "AIDS is over, right?", for the Day Without Art, December 1, 1998; Oversize poster (Folder 1)
- "AIDS: It's not a problem anymore- right, Mom?" for the Day Without Art, December 1, 1998; Oversize poster (Folder 1)
- "Sisters in Arms" poem poster, signed by Audre Lorde, 1988 (Folder 1)
- Flyer for Toshi Reagon/Sara Cytron event, July 18, 1998 (Folder 1)
- Flyer advertising workshops by Jan Phillips, author of Marry Your Muse (Folder 1)
- "The Artist's Creed" poem poster, 1998 (Folder 1)
- 2 posters for the Austin Festival of Dance, benefitting the AIDS Services of Austin, March 1994 (Folder 1)
- Cornellians at the March on Washington, 1986?; Oversize poster (Folder 1)
- Cornell student photo of protesters at the March on Washington, 1986? (Folder 1)
- Cornell student photos: one of the Names Quilt at the National Mall in D.C., one of two women carrying a panel in the D.C. march, 1986 (Folder 1)
- "What Does Koch Plan To Do About AIDS?" ACT-UP poster (Folder 1)
- "10,000 New York City AIDS Deaths" ACT-UP poster (Folder 1)
- "The Government Has Blood On Its Hands" AIDS related poster (Folder 1)
- "Making a Case for Community History" screening poster, by the GLBT Historical Society, June 2000 (Folder 1)
- "Columbus Ohio Gay Pride Parade 1983", 1983; Black and white fabric flag (15"x16") (Folder 1)
- Respect ALL Families poster (COLAGE Children of Lesbians And Gays Everywhere) (Folder 1)
- Respect All Families poster(COLAGE Children of Lesbians and Gays Everywhere) (Folder 1)
- An original silk screened poster carried at the October 11, 1987 March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights, rescued from a trash can by Susan von Salis at the end of the march., October 11, 1987 (Folder 1)
- Buck Angel poster, Undated (Folder 1)
- "Word is out", 26 gay Americans, Undated (Folder 1)
- Art against AIDS, Undated (Folder 1)